item	cond	Q1	Q1O1	Q1O2	Q1O3	Q1corr_ans	Q2	Q2O1	Q2O2	Q2O3	Q2corr_ans	Q3	Q3O1	Q3O2	Q3O3	Q3corr_ans
1	1	The Bishop sent a thank you letter to the top donor every year. Who would receive this letter?  	 Mr.Roberts	 Dwights	There is not enough information	3	Mr. Roberts was standing in front of the alter facing it. What direction would he need to go in order to walk to where the secret chamber is thought to be? 	 Left	 Right	There is not enough information	3	The number of people attending service at the chapel has	Increased	Decreased	There is not enough information	2
1	2	The Bishop sent a thank you letter to the top donor every year. Who would receive this letter?  	 Mr.Roberts	 Dwights	There is not enough information	2	Mr. Roberts was standing in front of the alter facing it. What direction would he need to go in order to walk to where the secret chamber is thought to be? 	 Left	 Right	There is not enough information	1	The number of people attending service at the chapel has	Increased	Decreased	There is not enough information	2
1	3	The Bishop sent a thank you letter to the top donor every year. Who would receive this letter?  	 Mr.Roberts	 Dwights	There is not enough information	3	Mr. Roberts was standing in front of the alter facing it. What direction would he need to go in order to walk to where the secret chamber is thought to be? 	 Left	 Right	There is not enough information	1	The number of people attending service at the chapel has	Increased	Decreased	There is not enough information	2
1	4	The Bishop sent a thank you letter to the top donor every year. Who would receive this letter?  	 Mr.Roberts	 Dwights	There is not enough information	2	Mr. Roberts was standing in front of the alter facing it. What direction would he need to go in order to walk to where the secret chamber is thought to be? 	 Left	 Right	There is not enough information	3	The number of people attending service at the chapel has	Increased	Decreased	There is not enough information	2
1	5	Mr. Roberts was standing in front of the alter facing it. What direction would he need to go in order to walk to where the secret chamber is thought to be? 	 Left	 Right	There is not enough information	3	The Bishop sent a thank you letter to the top donor every year. Who would receive this letter?  	 Mr.Roberts	 Dwights	There is not enough information	3	The number of people attending service at the chapel has	Increased	Decreased	There is not enough information	2
1	6	Mr. Roberts was standing in front of the alter facing it. What direction would he need to go in order to walk to where the secret chamber is thought to be? 	 Left	 Right	There is not enough information	1	The Bishop sent a thank you letter to the top donor every year. Who would receive this letter?  	 Mr.Roberts	 Dwights	There is not enough information	2	The number of people attending service at the chapel has	Increased	Decreased	There is not enough information	2
1	7	Mr. Roberts was standing in front of the alter facing it. What direction would he need to go in order to walk to where the secret chamber is thought to be? 	 Left	 Right	There is not enough information	3	The Bishop sent a thank you letter to the top donor every year. Who would receive this letter?  	 Mr.Roberts	 Dwights	There is not enough information	2	The number of people attending service at the chapel has	Increased	Decreased	There is not enough information	2
1	8	Mr. Roberts was standing in front of the alter facing it. What direction would he need to go in order to walk to where the secret chamber is thought to be? 	 Left	 Right	There is not enough information	1	The Bishop sent a thank you letter to the top donor every year. Who would receive this letter?  	 Mr.Roberts	 Dwights	There is not enough information	3	The number of people attending service at the chapel has	Increased	Decreased	There is not enough information	2
2	1	"Every year there is a race to the top of the mountain which allows only the best to compete, who is most likely to qualify?"	Bradley 	 Sam	There is not enough information	3	"Mountain Ranger Tim McMurphy is standing at the rest stop he wants to investigate the  place where tourists throw their rubbish away so that he can put a stop to it, where does he need to go?"	 Up the mountain	 Down the mountain	There is not enough information	3	The rest stop on the mountain is frequently used by  	Bird watchers	Bear hunters	There is not enough information	1
2	2	"Every year there is a race to the top of the mountain which allows only the best to compete, who is most likely to qualify?"	Bradley 	 Sam	There is not enough information	2	"Mountain Ranger Tim McMurphy is standing at the rest stop he wants to investigate the  place where tourists throw their rubbish away so that he can put a stop to it, where does he need to go?"	 Up the mountain	 Down the mountain	There is not enough information	2	The rest stop on the mountain is frequently used by  	Bird watchers	Bear hunters	There is not enough information	1
2	3	"Every year there is a race to the top of the mountain which allows only the best to compete, who is most likely to qualify?"	Bradley 	 Sam	There is not enough information	3	"Mountain Ranger Tim McMurphy is standing at the rest stop he wants to investigate the  place where tourists throw their rubbish away so that he can put a stop to it, where does he need to go?"	 Up the mountain	 Down the mountain	There is not enough information	2	The rest stop on the mountain is frequently used by  	Bird watchers	Bear hunters	There is not enough information	1
2	4	"Every year there is a race to the top of the mountain which allows only the best to compete, who is most likely to qualify?"	Bradley 	 Sam	There is not enough information	2	"Mountain Ranger Tim McMurphy is standing at the rest stop he wants to investigate the  place where tourists throw their rubbish away so that he can put a stop to it, where does he need to go?"	 Up the mountain	 Down the mountain	There is not enough information	3	The rest stop on the mountain is frequently used by  	Bird watchers	Bear hunters	There is not enough information	1
2	5	"Mountain Ranger Tim McMurphy is standing at the rest stop he wants to investigate the  place where tourists throw their rubbish away so that he can put a stop to it, where does he need to go?"	 Up the mountain	 Down the mountain	There is not enough information	3	"Every year there is a race to the top of the mountain which allows only the best to compete, who is most likely to qualify?"	Bradley 	 Sam	There is not enough information	3	The rest stop on the mountain is frequently used by  	Bird watchers	Bear hunters	There is not enough information	1
2	6	"Mountain Ranger Tim McMurphy is standing at the rest stop he wants to investigate the  place where tourists throw their rubbish away so that he can put a stop to it, where does he need to go?"	 Up the mountain	 Down the mountain	There is not enough information	2	"Every year there is a race to the top of the mountain which allows only the best to compete, who is most likely to qualify?"	Bradley 	 Sam	There is not enough information	2	The rest stop on the mountain is frequently used by  	Bird watchers	Bear hunters	There is not enough information	1
2	7	"Mountain Ranger Tim McMurphy is standing at the rest stop he wants to investigate the  place where tourists throw their rubbish away so that he can put a stop to it, where does he need to go?"	 Up the mountain	 Down the mountain	There is not enough information	3	"Every year there is a race to the top of the mountain which allows only the best to compete, who is most likely to qualify?"	Bradley 	 Sam	There is not enough information	2	The rest stop on the mountain is frequently used by  	Bird watchers	Bear hunters	There is not enough information	1
2	8	"Mountain Ranger Tim McMurphy is standing at the rest stop he wants to investigate the  place where tourists throw their rubbish away so that he can put a stop to it, where does he need to go?"	 Up the mountain	 Down the mountain	There is not enough information	2	"Every year there is a race to the top of the mountain which allows only the best to compete, who is most likely to qualify?"	Bradley 	 Sam	There is not enough information	3	The rest stop on the mountain is frequently used by  	Bird watchers	Bear hunters	There is not enough information	1
3	1	A survey has taken responses from people who visit the surgery which asks which GP they prefer to go to based on their personality. Who is the most popular GP in town?	Malcom	Sue	There is not enough information	3	"The cleaner is standing in the small play park and wants to polish the surgery’s floors, which way does he need to go to pick up his floor polisher?"	 Ahead 	Back towards the surgery	There is not enough information	3	The town’s surgery has recently___	Been refurbished 	Burned down	There is not enough information	1
3	2	A survey has taken responses from people who visit the surgery which asks which GP they prefer to go to based on their personality. Who is the most popular GP in town?	Malcom	Sue	There is not enough information	2	"The cleaner is standing in the small play park and wants to polish the surgery’s floors, which way does he need to go to pick up his floor polisher?"	 Ahead 	Back towards the surgery	There is not enough information	2	The town’s surgery has recently___	Been refurbished 	Burned down	There is not enough information	1
3	3	A survey has taken responses from people who visit the surgery which asks which GP they prefer to go to based on their personality. Who is the most popular GP in town?	Malcom	Sue	There is not enough information	3	"The cleaner is standing in the small play park and wants to polish the surgery’s floors, which way does he need to go to pick up his floor polisher?"	 Ahead 	Back towards the surgery	There is not enough information	2	The town’s surgery has recently___	Been refurbished 	Burned down	There is not enough information	1
3	4	A survey has taken responses from people who visit the surgery which asks which GP they prefer to go to based on their personality. Who is the most popular GP in town?	Malcom	Sue	There is not enough information	2	"The cleaner is standing in the small play park and wants to polish the surgery’s floors, which way does he need to go to pick up his floor polisher?"	 Ahead 	Back towards the surgery	There is not enough information	3	The town’s surgery has recently___	Been refurbished 	Burned down	There is not enough information	1
3	5	"The cleaner is standing in the small play park and wants to polish the surgery’s floors, which way does he need to go to pick up his floor polisher?"	 Ahead 	Back towards the surgery	There is not enough information	3	A survey has taken responses from people who visit the surgery which asks which GP they prefer to go to based on their personality. Who is the most popular GP in town?	Malcom	Sue	There is not enough information	3	The town’s surgery has recently___	Been refurbished 	Burned down	There is not enough information	1
3	6	"The cleaner is standing in the small play park and wants to polish the surgery’s floors, which way does he need to go to pick up his floor polisher?"	 Ahead 	Back towards the surgery	There is not enough information	2	A survey has taken responses from people who visit the surgery which asks which GP they prefer to go to based on their personality. Who is the most popular GP in town?	Malcom	Sue	There is not enough information	2	The town’s surgery has recently___	Been refurbished 	Burned down	There is not enough information	1
3	7	"The cleaner is standing in the small play park and wants to polish the surgery’s floors, which way does he need to go to pick up his floor polisher?"	 Ahead 	Back towards the surgery	There is not enough information	3	A survey has taken responses from people who visit the surgery which asks which GP they prefer to go to based on their personality. Who is the most popular GP in town?	Malcom	Sue	There is not enough information	2	The town’s surgery has recently___	Been refurbished 	Burned down	There is not enough information	1
3	8	"The cleaner is standing in the small play park and wants to polish the surgery’s floors, which way does he need to go to pick up his floor polisher?"	 Ahead 	Back towards the surgery	There is not enough information	2	A survey has taken responses from people who visit the surgery which asks which GP they prefer to go to based on their personality. Who is the most popular GP in town?	Malcom	Sue	There is not enough information	3	The town’s surgery has recently___	Been refurbished 	Burned down	There is not enough information	1
4	1	"A local fisherman’s boat has recently broken down, the fisherman doesn’t want to delay the lighthouse repair too much but also needs his boat fixed so decides to ask the least best mechanic to help him. Whom should he ask?"	Susan	Benjamin  	There is not enough information	3	"Allan is standing in front of the weather station facing it, he wants to buy some coffee for his friends so they can take a break, in which direction does he need to go?"	 Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	The Island has a ___ population	Large	Small	There is not enough information	2
4	2	"A local fisherman’s boat has recently broken down, the fisherman doesn’t want to delay the lighthouse repair too much but also needs his boat fixed so decides to ask the least best mechanic to help him. Whom should he ask?"	Susan	Benjamin  	There is not enough information	2	"Allan is standing in front of the weather station facing it, he wants to buy some coffee for his friends so they can take a break, in which direction does he need to go?"	 Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	The Island has a ___ population	Large	Small	There is not enough information	2
4	3	"A local fisherman’s boat has recently broken down, the fisherman doesn’t want to delay the lighthouse repair too much but also needs his boat fixed so decides to ask the least best mechanic to help him. Whom should he ask?"	Susan	Benjamin  	There is not enough information	3	"Allan is standing in front of the weather station facing it, he wants to buy some coffee for his friends so they can take a break, in which direction does he need to go?"	 Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	The Island has a ___ population	Large	Small	There is not enough information	2
4	4	"A local fisherman’s boat has recently broken down, the fisherman doesn’t want to delay the lighthouse repair too much but also needs his boat fixed so decides to ask the least best mechanic to help him. Whom should he ask?"	Susan	Benjamin  	There is not enough information	2	"Allan is standing in front of the weather station facing it, he wants to buy some coffee for his friends so they can take a break, in which direction does he need to go?"	 Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	The Island has a ___ population	Large	Small	There is not enough information	2
4	5	"Allan is standing in front of the weather station facing it, he wants to buy some coffee for his friends so they can take a break, in which direction does he need to go?"	 Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	"A local fisherman’s boat has recently broken down, the fisherman doesn’t want to delay the lighthouse repair too much but also needs his boat fixed so decides to ask the least best mechanic to help him. Whom should he ask?"	Susan	Benjamin  	There is not enough information	3	The Island has a ___ population	Large	Small	There is not enough information	2
4	6	"Allan is standing in front of the weather station facing it, he wants to buy some coffee for his friends so they can take a break, in which direction does he need to go?"	 Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	"A local fisherman’s boat has recently broken down, the fisherman doesn’t want to delay the lighthouse repair too much but also needs his boat fixed so decides to ask the least best mechanic to help him. Whom should he ask?"	Susan	Benjamin  	There is not enough information	2	The Island has a ___ population	Large	Small	There is not enough information	2
4	7	"Allan is standing in front of the weather station facing it, he wants to buy some coffee for his friends so they can take a break, in which direction does he need to go?"	 Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	"A local fisherman’s boat has recently broken down, the fisherman doesn’t want to delay the lighthouse repair too much but also needs his boat fixed so decides to ask the least best mechanic to help him. Whom should he ask?"	Susan	Benjamin  	There is not enough information	2	The Island has a ___ population	Large	Small	There is not enough information	2
4	8	"Allan is standing in front of the weather station facing it, he wants to buy some coffee for his friends so they can take a break, in which direction does he need to go?"	 Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	"A local fisherman’s boat has recently broken down, the fisherman doesn’t want to delay the lighthouse repair too much but also needs his boat fixed so decides to ask the least best mechanic to help him. Whom should he ask?"	Susan	Benjamin  	There is not enough information	3	The Island has a ___ population	Large	Small	There is not enough information	2
5	1	The Caves of Lincoln gorge can be dangerous to the inexperienced caver. Who in Terrance’s family is the least experienced?	Terrance	Stephen	There is not enough information	3	"Joan has decided she wants to be the first in the undiscovered cavern at Lincoln gorge, she is currently at the rest stop. In which direction would she need to go to find it? "	Up	Down	There is not enough information	3	Terrance’s biological father is called___	Andrew	Balthazar	There is not enough information	3
5	2	The Caves of Lincoln gorge can be dangerous to the inexperienced caver. Who in Terrance’s family is the least experienced?	Terrance	Stephen	There is not enough information	1	"Joan has decided she wants to be the first in the undiscovered cavern at Lincoln gorge, she is currently at the rest stop. In which direction would she need to go to find it? "	Up	Down	There is not enough information	1	Terrance’s biological father is called___	Andrew	Balthazar	There is not enough information	3
5	3	The Caves of Lincoln gorge can be dangerous to the inexperienced caver. Who in Terrance’s family is the least experienced?	Terrance	Stephen	There is not enough information	3	"Joan has decided she wants to be the first in the undiscovered cavern at Lincoln gorge, she is currently at the rest stop. In which direction would she need to go to find it? "	Up	Down	There is not enough information	1	Terrance’s biological father is called___	Andrew	Balthazar	There is not enough information	3
5	4	The Caves of Lincoln gorge can be dangerous to the inexperienced caver. Who in Terrance’s family is the least experienced?	Terrance	Stephen	There is not enough information	1	"Joan has decided she wants to be the first in the undiscovered cavern at Lincoln gorge, she is currently at the rest stop. In which direction would she need to go to find it? "	Up	Down	There is not enough information	3	Terrance’s biological father is called___	Andrew	Balthazar	There is not enough information	3
5	5	"Joan has decided she wants to be the first in the undiscovered cavern at Lincoln gorge, she is currently at the rest stop. In which direction would she need to go to find it? "	Up	Down	There is not enough information	3	The Caves of Lincoln gorge can be dangerous to the inexperienced caver. Who in Terrance’s family is the least experienced?	Terrance	Stephen	There is not enough information	3	Terrance’s biological father is called___	Andrew	Balthazar	There is not enough information	3
5	6	"Joan has decided she wants to be the first in the undiscovered cavern at Lincoln gorge, she is currently at the rest stop. In which direction would she need to go to find it? "	Up	Down	There is not enough information	1	The Caves of Lincoln gorge can be dangerous to the inexperienced caver. Who in Terrance’s family is the least experienced?	Terrance	Stephen	There is not enough information	1	Terrance’s biological father is called___	Andrew	Balthazar	There is not enough information	3
5	7	"Joan has decided she wants to be the first in the undiscovered cavern at Lincoln gorge, she is currently at the rest stop. In which direction would she need to go to find it? "	Up	Down	There is not enough information	3	The Caves of Lincoln gorge can be dangerous to the inexperienced caver. Who in Terrance’s family is the least experienced?	Terrance	Stephen	There is not enough information	1	Terrance’s biological father is called___	Andrew	Balthazar	There is not enough information	3
5	8	"Joan has decided she wants to be the first in the undiscovered cavern at Lincoln gorge, she is currently at the rest stop. In which direction would she need to go to find it? "	Up	Down	There is not enough information	1	The Caves of Lincoln gorge can be dangerous to the inexperienced caver. Who in Terrance’s family is the least experienced?	Terrance	Stephen	There is not enough information	3	Terrance’s biological father is called___	Andrew	Balthazar	There is not enough information	3
6	1	"A car thief is in Harriet’s neighbourhood and wants to make away with the most expensive car, who’s car does he steal? "	Harriet’s	Olive’s	There is not enough information	3	"Harriet is being randomly searched by the police stop and search operation. She decides that she wants to have a coffee after the police are done, before continuing on her journey. Which way does she need to head?"	Towards the bridge	Away from the bridge 	There is not enough information	3	Harriet ____ Barry 	Likes	Dislikes	There is not enough information	2
6	2	"A car thief is in Harriet’s neighbourhood and wants to make away with the most expensive car, who’s car does he steal? "	Harriet’s	Olive’s	There is not enough information	1	"Harriet is being randomly searched by the police stop and search operation. She decides that she wants to have a coffee after the police are done, before continuing on her journey. Which way does she need to head?"	Towards the bridge	Away from the bridge 	There is not enough information	1	Harriet ____ Barry 	Likes	Dislikes	There is not enough information	2
6	3	"A car thief is in Harriet’s neighbourhood and wants to make away with the most expensive car, who’s car does he steal? "	Harriet’s	Olive’s	There is not enough information	3	"Harriet is being randomly searched by the police stop and search operation. She decides that she wants to have a coffee after the police are done, before continuing on her journey. Which way does she need to head?"	Towards the bridge	Away from the bridge 	There is not enough information	1	Harriet ____ Barry 	Likes	Dislikes	There is not enough information	2
6	4	"A car thief is in Harriet’s neighbourhood and wants to make away with the most expensive car, who’s car does he steal? "	Harriet’s	Olive’s	There is not enough information	1	"Harriet is being randomly searched by the police stop and search operation. She decides that she wants to have a coffee after the police are done, before continuing on her journey. Which way does she need to head?"	Towards the bridge	Away from the bridge 	There is not enough information	3	Harriet ____ Barry 	Likes	Dislikes	There is not enough information	2
6	5	"Harriet is being randomly searched by the police stop and search operation. She decides that she wants to have a coffee after the police are done, before continuing on her journey. Which way does she need to head?"	Towards the bridge	Away from the bridge 	There is not enough information	3	"A car thief is in Harriet’s neighbourhood and wants to make away with the most expensive car, who’s car does he steal? "	Harriet’s	Olive’s	There is not enough information	3	Harriet ____ Barry 	Likes	Dislikes	There is not enough information	2
6	6	"Harriet is being randomly searched by the police stop and search operation. She decides that she wants to have a coffee after the police are done, before continuing on her journey. Which way does she need to head?"	Towards the bridge	Away from the bridge 	There is not enough information	1	"A car thief is in Harriet’s neighbourhood and wants to make away with the most expensive car, who’s car does he steal? "	Harriet’s	Olive’s	There is not enough information	1	Harriet ____ Barry 	Likes	Dislikes	There is not enough information	2
6	7	"Harriet is being randomly searched by the police stop and search operation. She decides that she wants to have a coffee after the police are done, before continuing on her journey. Which way does she need to head?"	Towards the bridge	Away from the bridge 	There is not enough information	3	"A car thief is in Harriet’s neighbourhood and wants to make away with the most expensive car, who’s car does he steal? "	Harriet’s	Olive’s	There is not enough information	1	Harriet ____ Barry 	Likes	Dislikes	There is not enough information	2
6	8	"Harriet is being randomly searched by the police stop and search operation. She decides that she wants to have a coffee after the police are done, before continuing on her journey. Which way does she need to head?"	Towards the bridge	Away from the bridge 	There is not enough information	1	"A car thief is in Harriet’s neighbourhood and wants to make away with the most expensive car, who’s car does he steal? "	Harriet’s	Olive’s	There is not enough information	3	Harriet ____ Barry 	Likes	Dislikes	There is not enough information	2
7	1	"The School board is deciding which departments should receive  more funding for the next year and have decided  the basketball team would receive the most funding, who should receive the second most amount of funding based on it’s popularity?"	The football team 	The art department	There is not enough information	3	In order to get from the refreshment’s table to the photo booth which way would one have to go to get to the table with well wishes?	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	The theme of the Prom is___	1950’s	1960’s 	There is not enough information	1
7	2	"The School board is deciding which departments should receive  more funding for the next year and have decided  the basketball team would receive the most funding, who should receive the second most amount of funding based on it’s popularity?"	The football team 	The art department	There is not enough information	2	In order to get from the refreshment’s table to the photo booth which way would one have to go to get to the table with well wishes?	Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	The theme of the Prom is___	1950’s	1960’s 	There is not enough information	1
7	3	"The School board is deciding which departments should receive  more funding for the next year and have decided  the basketball team would receive the most funding, who should receive the second most amount of funding based on it’s popularity?"	The football team 	The art department	There is not enough information	3	In order to get from the refreshment’s table to the photo booth which way would one have to go to get to the table with well wishes?	Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	The theme of the Prom is___	1950’s	1960’s 	There is not enough information	1
7	4	"The School board is deciding which departments should receive  more funding for the next year and have decided  the basketball team would receive the most funding, who should receive the second most amount of funding based on it’s popularity?"	The football team 	The art department	There is not enough information	2	In order to get from the refreshment’s table to the photo booth which way would one have to go to get to the table with well wishes?	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	The theme of the Prom is___	1950’s	1960’s 	There is not enough information	1
7	5	In order to get from the refreshment’s table to the photo booth which way would one have to go to get to the table with well wishes?	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	"The School board is deciding which departments should receive  more funding for the next year and have decided  the basketball team would receive the most funding, who should receive the second most amount of funding based on it’s popularity?"	The football team 	The art department	There is not enough information	3	The theme of the Prom is___	1950’s	1960’s 	There is not enough information	1
7	6	In order to get from the refreshment’s table to the photo booth which way would one have to go to get to the table with well wishes?	Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	"The School board is deciding which departments should receive  more funding for the next year and have decided  the basketball team would receive the most funding, who should receive the second most amount of funding based on it’s popularity?"	The football team 	The art department	There is not enough information	2	The theme of the Prom is___	1950’s	1960’s 	There is not enough information	1
7	7	In order to get from the refreshment’s table to the photo booth which way would one have to go to get to the table with well wishes?	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	"The School board is deciding which departments should receive  more funding for the next year and have decided  the basketball team would receive the most funding, who should receive the second most amount of funding based on it’s popularity?"	The football team 	The art department	There is not enough information	2	The theme of the Prom is___	1950’s	1960’s 	There is not enough information	1
7	8	In order to get from the refreshment’s table to the photo booth which way would one have to go to get to the table with well wishes?	Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	"The School board is deciding which departments should receive  more funding for the next year and have decided  the basketball team would receive the most funding, who should receive the second most amount of funding based on it’s popularity?"	The football team 	The art department	There is not enough information	3	The theme of the Prom is___	1950’s	1960’s 	There is not enough information	1
8	1	"After the marathon the three friends decide to compete with only each other, who is most likely to win?"	Dustin	Ralph 	There is not enough information	3	The Mayor of Dunwich has decided that he would personally reward the top big charity running team with donations of £500. Which charity is most likely to receive  this donation from the Mayor?	The wildlife charity 	The cancer charity 	There is not enough information	3	The Dunwich draws crowds from all over the___ 	County	Town	There is not enough information	1
8	2	"After the marathon the three friends decide to compete with only each other, who is most likely to win?"	Dustin	Ralph 	There is not enough information	2	The Mayor of Dunwich has decided that he would personally reward the top big charity running team with donations of £500. Which charity is most likely to receive  this donation from the Mayor?	The wildlife charity 	The cancer charity 	There is not enough information	1	The Dunwich draws crowds from all over the___ 	County	Town	There is not enough information	1
8	3	"After the marathon the three friends decide to compete with only each other, who is most likely to win?"	Dustin	Ralph 	There is not enough information	3	The Mayor of Dunwich has decided that he would personally reward the top big charity running team with donations of £500. Which charity is most likely to receive  this donation from the Mayor?	The wildlife charity 	The cancer charity 	There is not enough information	1	The Dunwich draws crowds from all over the___ 	County	Town	There is not enough information	1
8	4	"After the marathon the three friends decide to compete with only each other, who is most likely to win?"	Dustin	Ralph 	There is not enough information	2	The Mayor of Dunwich has decided that he would personally reward the top big charity running team with donations of £500. Which charity is most likely to receive  this donation from the Mayor?	The wildlife charity 	The cancer charity 	There is not enough information	3	The Dunwich draws crowds from all over the___ 	County	Town	There is not enough information	1
8	5	The Mayor of Dunwich has decided that he would personally reward the top big charity running team with donations of £500. Which charity is most likely to receive  this donation from the Mayor?	The wildlife charity 	The cancer charity 	There is not enough information	3	"After the marathon the three friends decide to compete with only each other, who is most likely to win?"	Dustin	Ralph 	There is not enough information	3	The Dunwich draws crowds from all over the___ 	County	Town	There is not enough information	1
8	6	The Mayor of Dunwich has decided that he would personally reward the top big charity running team with donations of £500. Which charity is most likely to receive  this donation from the Mayor?	The wildlife charity 	The cancer charity 	There is not enough information	1	"After the marathon the three friends decide to compete with only each other, who is most likely to win?"	Dustin	Ralph 	There is not enough information	2	The Dunwich draws crowds from all over the___ 	County	Town	There is not enough information	1
8	7	The Mayor of Dunwich has decided that he would personally reward the top big charity running team with donations of £500. Which charity is most likely to receive  this donation from the Mayor?	The wildlife charity 	The cancer charity 	There is not enough information	3	"After the marathon the three friends decide to compete with only each other, who is most likely to win?"	Dustin	Ralph 	There is not enough information	2	The Dunwich draws crowds from all over the___ 	County	Town	There is not enough information	1
8	8	The Mayor of Dunwich has decided that he would personally reward the top big charity running team with donations of £500. Which charity is most likely to receive  this donation from the Mayor?	The wildlife charity 	The cancer charity 	There is not enough information	1	"After the marathon the three friends decide to compete with only each other, who is most likely to win?"	Dustin	Ralph 	There is not enough information	3	The Dunwich draws crowds from all over the___ 	County	Town	There is not enough information	1
9	1	"Jonathan, Catherine and Thom are the first to arrive at the exclusive lodge this season, who is the least wealthy out of all of them?"	Catherine	Thom 	There is not enough information	3	The Lodge is urgently looking for the missing child. A local police man is at the lodge and decides to look for the child himself which way should he head?	Up 	Down	There is not enough information	3	The Ski resort caters to	Wealthy people	People on a budget 	There is not enough information	1
9	2	"Jonathan, Catherine and Thom are the first to arrive at the exclusive lodge this season, who is the least wealthy out of all of them?"	Catherine	Thom 	There is not enough information	2	The Lodge is urgently looking for the missing child. A local police man is at the lodge and decides to look for the child himself which way should he head?	Up 	Down	There is not enough information	1	The Ski resort caters to	Wealthy people	People on a budget 	There is not enough information	1
9	3	"Jonathan, Catherine and Thom are the first to arrive at the exclusive lodge this season, who is the least wealthy out of all of them?"	Catherine	Thom 	There is not enough information	3	The Lodge is urgently looking for the missing child. A local police man is at the lodge and decides to look for the child himself which way should he head?	Up 	Down	There is not enough information	1	The Ski resort caters to	Wealthy people	People on a budget 	There is not enough information	1
9	4	"Jonathan, Catherine and Thom are the first to arrive at the exclusive lodge this season, who is the least wealthy out of all of them?"	Catherine	Thom 	There is not enough information	2	The Lodge is urgently looking for the missing child. A local police man is at the lodge and decides to look for the child himself which way should he head?	Up 	Down	There is not enough information	3	The Ski resort caters to	Wealthy people	People on a budget 	There is not enough information	1
9	5	The Lodge is urgently looking for the missing child. A local police man is at the lodge and decides to look for the child himself which way should he head?	Up 	Down	There is not enough information	3	"Jonathan, Catherine and Thom are the first to arrive at the exclusive lodge this season, who is the least wealthy out of all of them?"	Catherine	Thom 	There is not enough information	3	The Ski resort caters to	Wealthy people	People on a budget 	There is not enough information	1
9	6	The Lodge is urgently looking for the missing child. A local police man is at the lodge and decides to look for the child himself which way should he head?	Up 	Down	There is not enough information	1	"Jonathan, Catherine and Thom are the first to arrive at the exclusive lodge this season, who is the least wealthy out of all of them?"	Catherine	Thom 	There is not enough information	2	The Ski resort caters to	Wealthy people	People on a budget 	There is not enough information	1
9	7	The Lodge is urgently looking for the missing child. A local police man is at the lodge and decides to look for the child himself which way should he head?	Up 	Down	There is not enough information	3	"Jonathan, Catherine and Thom are the first to arrive at the exclusive lodge this season, who is the least wealthy out of all of them?"	Catherine	Thom 	There is not enough information	2	The Ski resort caters to	Wealthy people	People on a budget 	There is not enough information	1
9	8	The Lodge is urgently looking for the missing child. A local police man is at the lodge and decides to look for the child himself which way should he head?	Up 	Down	There is not enough information	1	"Jonathan, Catherine and Thom are the first to arrive at the exclusive lodge this season, who is the least wealthy out of all of them?"	Catherine	Thom 	There is not enough information	3	The Ski resort caters to	Wealthy people	People on a budget 	There is not enough information	1
10	1	"The council is giving away a prize for the finest garden in the county, Agatha Sam and Rachel have all entered their gardens into the competition.  Who  is most likely to win? "	Agatha	Rachel	There is not enough information	3	Sam wants to get rid of the plastic plants that have been disrupting her business. She is standing infront of the succulents and indoor plants in which direction should she look to find the plastic plants?	Right	Left 	There is not enough information	3	The Flower Shop is located on	 Wensley High Street	 Toucan Drive 	There is not enough information	1
10	2	"The council is giving away a prize for the finest garden in the county, Agatha Sam and Rachel have all entered their gardens into the competition.  Who  is most likely to win? "	Agatha	Rachel	There is not enough information	1	Sam wants to get rid of the plastic plants that have been disrupting her business. She is standing infront of the succulents and indoor plants in which direction should she look to find the plastic plants?	Right	Left 	There is not enough information	2	The Flower Shop is located on	 Wensley High Street	 Toucan Drive 	There is not enough information	1
10	3	"The council is giving away a prize for the finest garden in the county, Agatha Sam and Rachel have all entered their gardens into the competition.  Who  is most likely to win? "	Agatha	Rachel	There is not enough information	3	Sam wants to get rid of the plastic plants that have been disrupting her business. She is standing infront of the succulents and indoor plants in which direction should she look to find the plastic plants?	Right	Left 	There is not enough information	2	The Flower Shop is located on	 Wensley High Street	 Toucan Drive 	There is not enough information	1
10	4	"The council is giving away a prize for the finest garden in the county, Agatha Sam and Rachel have all entered their gardens into the competition.  Who  is most likely to win? "	Agatha	Rachel	There is not enough information	1	Sam wants to get rid of the plastic plants that have been disrupting her business. She is standing infront of the succulents and indoor plants in which direction should she look to find the plastic plants?	Right	Left 	There is not enough information	3	The Flower Shop is located on	 Wensley High Street	 Toucan Drive 	There is not enough information	1
10	5	Sam wants to get rid of the plastic plants that have been disrupting her business. She is standing infront of the succulents and indoor plants in which direction should she look to find the plastic plants?	Right	Left 	There is not enough information	3	"The council is giving away a prize for the finest garden in the county, Agatha Sam and Rachel have all entered their gardens into the competition.  Who  is most likely to win? "	Agatha	Rachel	There is not enough information	3	The Flower Shop is located on	 Wensley High Street	 Toucan Drive 	There is not enough information	1
10	6	Sam wants to get rid of the plastic plants that have been disrupting her business. She is standing infront of the succulents and indoor plants in which direction should she look to find the plastic plants?	Right	Left 	There is not enough information	2	"The council is giving away a prize for the finest garden in the county, Agatha Sam and Rachel have all entered their gardens into the competition.  Who  is most likely to win? "	Agatha	Rachel	There is not enough information	1	The Flower Shop is located on	 Wensley High Street	 Toucan Drive 	There is not enough information	1
10	7	Sam wants to get rid of the plastic plants that have been disrupting her business. She is standing infront of the succulents and indoor plants in which direction should she look to find the plastic plants?	Right	Left 	There is not enough information	3	"The council is giving away a prize for the finest garden in the county, Agatha Sam and Rachel have all entered their gardens into the competition.  Who  is most likely to win? "	Agatha	Rachel	There is not enough information	1	The Flower Shop is located on	 Wensley High Street	 Toucan Drive 	There is not enough information	1
10	8	Sam wants to get rid of the plastic plants that have been disrupting her business. She is standing infront of the succulents and indoor plants in which direction should she look to find the plastic plants?	Right	Left 	There is not enough information	2	"The council is giving away a prize for the finest garden in the county, Agatha Sam and Rachel have all entered their gardens into the competition.  Who  is most likely to win? "	Agatha	Rachel	There is not enough information	3	The Flower Shop is located on	 Wensley High Street	 Toucan Drive 	There is not enough information	1
11	1	Ian is new in the village and his family wants him to make friends with respected families. Out of the three friends who is Ian least likely to pick? 	Sally	Joanna 	There is not enough information	3	A holiday maker has lost his watch by the stream.  He is standing infront of the monument to the brave dog with his back towards the summer lodges. Which way should he go to try and find his watch ? 	 Ahead	Back 	There is not enough information	3	The Monument behind the summer lodges is to commemorate	 The soldiers that fought in the First World War 	 A dog that saved its owners life	There is not enough information	2
11	2	Ian is new in the village and his family wants him to make friends with respected families. Out of the three friends who is Ian least likely to pick? 	Sally	Joanna 	There is not enough information	2	A holiday maker has lost his watch by the stream.  He is standing infront of the monument to the brave dog with his back towards the summer lodges. Which way should he go to try and find his watch ? 	 Ahead	Back 	There is not enough information	2	The Monument behind the summer lodges is to commemorate	 The soldiers that fought in the First World War 	 A dog that saved its owners life	There is not enough information	2
11	3	Ian is new in the village and his family wants him to make friends with respected families. Out of the three friends who is Ian least likely to pick? 	Sally	Joanna 	There is not enough information	3	A holiday maker has lost his watch by the stream.  He is standing infront of the monument to the brave dog with his back towards the summer lodges. Which way should he go to try and find his watch ? 	 Ahead	Back 	There is not enough information	2	The Monument behind the summer lodges is to commemorate	 The soldiers that fought in the First World War 	 A dog that saved its owners life	There is not enough information	2
11	4	Ian is new in the village and his family wants him to make friends with respected families. Out of the three friends who is Ian least likely to pick? 	Sally	Joanna 	There is not enough information	2	A holiday maker has lost his watch by the stream.  He is standing infront of the monument to the brave dog with his back towards the summer lodges. Which way should he go to try and find his watch ? 	 Ahead	Back 	There is not enough information	3	The Monument behind the summer lodges is to commemorate	 The soldiers that fought in the First World War 	 A dog that saved its owners life	There is not enough information	2
11	5	A holiday maker has lost his watch by the stream.  He is standing infront of the monument to the brave dog with his back towards the summer lodges. Which way should he go to try and find his watch ? 	 Ahead	Back 	There is not enough information	3	Ian is new in the village and his family wants him to make friends with respected families. Out of the three friends who is Ian least likely to pick? 	Sally	Joanna 	There is not enough information	3	The Monument behind the summer lodges is to commemorate	 The soldiers that fought in the First World War 	 A dog that saved its owners life	There is not enough information	2
11	6	A holiday maker has lost his watch by the stream.  He is standing infront of the monument to the brave dog with his back towards the summer lodges. Which way should he go to try and find his watch ? 	 Ahead	Back 	There is not enough information	2	Ian is new in the village and his family wants him to make friends with respected families. Out of the three friends who is Ian least likely to pick? 	Sally	Joanna 	There is not enough information	2	The Monument behind the summer lodges is to commemorate	 The soldiers that fought in the First World War 	 A dog that saved its owners life	There is not enough information	2
11	7	A holiday maker has lost his watch by the stream.  He is standing infront of the monument to the brave dog with his back towards the summer lodges. Which way should he go to try and find his watch ? 	 Ahead	Back 	There is not enough information	3	Ian is new in the village and his family wants him to make friends with respected families. Out of the three friends who is Ian least likely to pick? 	Sally	Joanna 	There is not enough information	2	The Monument behind the summer lodges is to commemorate	 The soldiers that fought in the First World War 	 A dog that saved its owners life	There is not enough information	2
11	8	A holiday maker has lost his watch by the stream.  He is standing infront of the monument to the brave dog with his back towards the summer lodges. Which way should he go to try and find his watch ? 	 Ahead	Back 	There is not enough information	2	Ian is new in the village and his family wants him to make friends with respected families. Out of the three friends who is Ian least likely to pick? 	Sally	Joanna 	There is not enough information	3	The Monument behind the summer lodges is to commemorate	 The soldiers that fought in the First World War 	 A dog that saved its owners life	There is not enough information	2
12	1	"Next year Taunton airfield will host a small air show, who is the most skilled pilot?"	Josh	Terry	There is not enough information	3	The helicopter pilot wants to know if he is flying higher than the biplane. Which aircraft is higher?	The Helicopter	The Biplane 	There is not enough information	3	Torton airfield is	Empty	Busy	There is not enough information	2
12	2	"Next year Taunton airfield will host a small air show, who is the most skilled pilot?"	Josh	Terry	There is not enough information	1	The helicopter pilot wants to know if he is flying higher than the biplane. Which aircraft is higher?	The Helicopter	The Biplane 	There is not enough information	1	Torton airfield is	Empty	Busy	There is not enough information	2
12	3	"Next year Taunton airfield will host a small air show, who is the most skilled pilot?"	Josh	Terry	There is not enough information	3	The helicopter pilot wants to know if he is flying higher than the biplane. Which aircraft is higher?	The Helicopter	The Biplane 	There is not enough information	1	Torton airfield is	Empty	Busy	There is not enough information	2
12	4	"Next year Taunton airfield will host a small air show, who is the most skilled pilot?"	Josh	Terry	There is not enough information	1	The helicopter pilot wants to know if he is flying higher than the biplane. Which aircraft is higher?	The Helicopter	The Biplane 	There is not enough information	3	Torton airfield is	Empty	Busy	There is not enough information	2
12	5	The helicopter pilot wants to know if he is flying higher than the biplane. Which aircraft is higher?	The Helicopter	The Biplane 	There is not enough information	3	"Next year Taunton airfield will host a small air show, who is the most skilled pilot?"	Josh	Terry	There is not enough information	3	Torton airfield is	Empty	Busy	There is not enough information	2
12	6	The helicopter pilot wants to know if he is flying higher than the biplane. Which aircraft is higher?	The Helicopter	The Biplane 	There is not enough information	1	"Next year Taunton airfield will host a small air show, who is the most skilled pilot?"	Josh	Terry	There is not enough information	1	Torton airfield is	Empty	Busy	There is not enough information	2
12	7	The helicopter pilot wants to know if he is flying higher than the biplane. Which aircraft is higher?	The Helicopter	The Biplane 	There is not enough information	3	"Next year Taunton airfield will host a small air show, who is the most skilled pilot?"	Josh	Terry	There is not enough information	1	Torton airfield is	Empty	Busy	There is not enough information	2
12	8	The helicopter pilot wants to know if he is flying higher than the biplane. Which aircraft is higher?	The Helicopter	The Biplane 	There is not enough information	1	"Next year Taunton airfield will host a small air show, who is the most skilled pilot?"	Josh	Terry	There is not enough information	3	Torton airfield is	Empty	Busy	There is not enough information	2
13	1	"The office has decided who should handle the Barbeque, who is least likely to help the person cooking?"	Ella 	Felix	There is not enough information	3	"The delivery man has come to the office with a large package containing the new fan, he is standing infront of the managers desk facing it but the manager has gone out for lunch. Where should he put the fan so that it is already where the manager wants it to be when she comes back?"	To the Left 	To the right 	There is not enough information	3	The office is very___	Hot	Cold	There is not enough information	1
13	2	"The office has decided who should handle the Barbeque, who is least likely to help the person cooking?"	Ella 	Felix	There is not enough information	1	"The delivery man has come to the office with a large package containing the new fan, he is standing infront of the managers desk facing it but the manager has gone out for lunch. Where should he put the fan so that it is already where the manager wants it to be when she comes back?"	To the Left 	To the right 	There is not enough information	1	The office is very___	Hot	Cold	There is not enough information	1
13	3	"The office has decided who should handle the Barbeque, who is least likely to help the person cooking?"	Ella 	Felix	There is not enough information	3	"The delivery man has come to the office with a large package containing the new fan, he is standing infront of the managers desk facing it but the manager has gone out for lunch. Where should he put the fan so that it is already where the manager wants it to be when she comes back?"	To the Left 	To the right 	There is not enough information	1	The office is very___	Hot	Cold	There is not enough information	1
13	4	"The office has decided who should handle the Barbeque, who is least likely to help the person cooking?"	Ella 	Felix	There is not enough information	1	"The delivery man has come to the office with a large package containing the new fan, he is standing infront of the managers desk facing it but the manager has gone out for lunch. Where should he put the fan so that it is already where the manager wants it to be when she comes back?"	To the Left 	To the right 	There is not enough information	3	The office is very___	Hot	Cold	There is not enough information	1
13	5	"The delivery man has come to the office with a large package containing the new fan, he is standing infront of the managers desk facing it but the manager has gone out for lunch. Where should he put the fan so that it is already where the manager wants it to be when she comes back?"	To the Left 	To the right 	There is not enough information	3	"The office has decided who should handle the Barbeque, who is least likely to help the person cooking?"	Ella 	Felix	There is not enough information	3	The office is very___	Hot	Cold	There is not enough information	1
13	6	"The delivery man has come to the office with a large package containing the new fan, he is standing infront of the managers desk facing it but the manager has gone out for lunch. Where should he put the fan so that it is already where the manager wants it to be when she comes back?"	To the Left 	To the right 	There is not enough information	1	"The office has decided who should handle the Barbeque, who is least likely to help the person cooking?"	Ella 	Felix	There is not enough information	1	The office is very___	Hot	Cold	There is not enough information	1
13	7	"The delivery man has come to the office with a large package containing the new fan, he is standing infront of the managers desk facing it but the manager has gone out for lunch. Where should he put the fan so that it is already where the manager wants it to be when she comes back?"	To the Left 	To the right 	There is not enough information	3	"The office has decided who should handle the Barbeque, who is least likely to help the person cooking?"	Ella 	Felix	There is not enough information	1	The office is very___	Hot	Cold	There is not enough information	1
13	8	"The delivery man has come to the office with a large package containing the new fan, he is standing infront of the managers desk facing it but the manager has gone out for lunch. Where should he put the fan so that it is already where the manager wants it to be when she comes back?"	To the Left 	To the right 	There is not enough information	1	"The office has decided who should handle the Barbeque, who is least likely to help the person cooking?"	Ella 	Felix	There is not enough information	3	The office is very___	Hot	Cold	There is not enough information	1
14	1	One of Daren’s former clients is having trouble with a recent job that Daren handled. He wants it fixed right away. Who should Daren send so that the best metal workers remain in the workshop to handle the 3 custom Jobs? 	Toby 	 Steve 	There is not enough information	3	Daren has decided to set up a humane trap for the mouse where should he put it?	Behind the lathe 	In front of the lathe	There is not enough information	3	What is the name of the street where Darren's workshop is located?	Yew Street	Guatemala Street	There is not enough information	1
14	2	One of Daren’s former clients is having trouble with a recent job that Daren handled. He wants it fixed right away. Who should Daren send so that the best metal workers remain in the workshop to handle the 3 custom Jobs? 	Toby 	 Steve 	There is not enough information	2	Daren has decided to set up a humane trap for the mouse where should he put it?	Behind the lathe 	In front of the lathe	There is not enough information	2	What is the name of the street where Darren's workshop is located?	Yew Street	Guatemala Street	There is not enough information	1
14	3	One of Daren’s former clients is having trouble with a recent job that Daren handled. He wants it fixed right away. Who should Daren send so that the best metal workers remain in the workshop to handle the 3 custom Jobs? 	Toby 	 Steve 	There is not enough information	3	Daren has decided to set up a humane trap for the mouse where should he put it?	Behind the lathe 	In front of the lathe	There is not enough information	2	What is the name of the street where Darren's workshop is located?	Yew Street	Guatemala Street	There is not enough information	1
14	4	One of Daren’s former clients is having trouble with a recent job that Daren handled. He wants it fixed right away. Who should Daren send so that the best metal workers remain in the workshop to handle the 3 custom Jobs? 	Toby 	 Steve 	There is not enough information	2	Daren has decided to set up a humane trap for the mouse where should he put it?	Behind the lathe 	In front of the lathe	There is not enough information	3	What is the name of the street where Darren's workshop is located?	Yew Street	Guatemala Street	There is not enough information	1
14	5	Daren has decided to set up a humane trap for the mouse where should he put it?	Behind the lathe 	In front of the lathe	There is not enough information	3	One of Daren’s former clients is having trouble with a recent job that Daren handled. He wants it fixed right away. Who should Daren send so that the best metal workers remain in the workshop to handle the 3 custom Jobs? 	Toby 	 Steve 	There is not enough information	3	What is the name of the street where Darren's workshop is located?	Yew Street	Guatemala Street	There is not enough information	1
14	6	Daren has decided to set up a humane trap for the mouse where should he put it?	Behind the lathe 	In front of the lathe	There is not enough information	2	One of Daren’s former clients is having trouble with a recent job that Daren handled. He wants it fixed right away. Who should Daren send so that the best metal workers remain in the workshop to handle the 3 custom Jobs? 	Toby 	 Steve 	There is not enough information	2	What is the name of the street where Darren's workshop is located?	Yew Street	Guatemala Street	There is not enough information	1
14	7	Daren has decided to set up a humane trap for the mouse where should he put it?	Behind the lathe 	In front of the lathe	There is not enough information	3	One of Daren’s former clients is having trouble with a recent job that Daren handled. He wants it fixed right away. Who should Daren send so that the best metal workers remain in the workshop to handle the 3 custom Jobs? 	Toby 	 Steve 	There is not enough information	2	What is the name of the street where Darren's workshop is located?	Yew Street	Guatemala Street	There is not enough information	1
14	8	Daren has decided to set up a humane trap for the mouse where should he put it?	Behind the lathe 	In front of the lathe	There is not enough information	2	One of Daren’s former clients is having trouble with a recent job that Daren handled. He wants it fixed right away. Who should Daren send so that the best metal workers remain in the workshop to handle the 3 custom Jobs? 	Toby 	 Steve 	There is not enough information	3	What is the name of the street where Darren's workshop is located?	Yew Street	Guatemala Street	There is not enough information	1
15	1	A tax investigation is launched that will assess work place bonuses. Who has received the biggest bonus out of Lucy and Linda? 	Lucy	Linda 	There is not enough information	3	The Foreman has decided to open up a new shaft. The Crew has assembled in the storage area in Shaft B. In which direction should they go to start the new mineshaft? 	Up	Down 	There is not enough information	3	The mine produces___	Iron	Copper 	There is not enough information	2
15	2	A tax investigation is launched that will assess work place bonuses. Who has received the biggest bonus out of Lucy and Linda? 	Lucy	Linda 	There is not enough information	2	The Foreman has decided to open up a new shaft. The Crew has assembled in the storage area in Shaft B. In which direction should they go to start the new mineshaft? 	Up	Down 	There is not enough information	2	The mine produces___	Iron	Copper 	There is not enough information	2
15	3	A tax investigation is launched that will assess work place bonuses. Who has received the biggest bonus out of Lucy and Linda? 	Lucy	Linda 	There is not enough information	3	The Foreman has decided to open up a new shaft. The Crew has assembled in the storage area in Shaft B. In which direction should they go to start the new mineshaft? 	Up	Down 	There is not enough information	2	The mine produces___	Iron	Copper 	There is not enough information	2
15	4	A tax investigation is launched that will assess work place bonuses. Who has received the biggest bonus out of Lucy and Linda? 	Lucy	Linda 	There is not enough information	2	The Foreman has decided to open up a new shaft. The Crew has assembled in the storage area in Shaft B. In which direction should they go to start the new mineshaft? 	Up	Down 	There is not enough information	3	The mine produces___	Iron	Copper 	There is not enough information	2
15	5	The Foreman has decided to open up a new shaft. The Crew has assembled in the storage area in Shaft B. In which direction should they go to start the new mineshaft? 	Up	Down 	There is not enough information	3	A tax investigation is launched that will assess work place bonuses. Who has received the biggest bonus out of Lucy and Linda? 	Lucy	Linda 	There is not enough information	3	The mine produces___	Iron	Copper 	There is not enough information	2
15	6	The Foreman has decided to open up a new shaft. The Crew has assembled in the storage area in Shaft B. In which direction should they go to start the new mineshaft? 	Up	Down 	There is not enough information	2	A tax investigation is launched that will assess work place bonuses. Who has received the biggest bonus out of Lucy and Linda? 	Lucy	Linda 	There is not enough information	2	The mine produces___	Iron	Copper 	There is not enough information	2
15	7	The Foreman has decided to open up a new shaft. The Crew has assembled in the storage area in Shaft B. In which direction should they go to start the new mineshaft? 	Up	Down 	There is not enough information	3	A tax investigation is launched that will assess work place bonuses. Who has received the biggest bonus out of Lucy and Linda? 	Lucy	Linda 	There is not enough information	2	The mine produces___	Iron	Copper 	There is not enough information	2
15	8	The Foreman has decided to open up a new shaft. The Crew has assembled in the storage area in Shaft B. In which direction should they go to start the new mineshaft? 	Up	Down 	There is not enough information	2	A tax investigation is launched that will assess work place bonuses. Who has received the biggest bonus out of Lucy and Linda? 	Lucy	Linda 	There is not enough information	3	The mine produces___	Iron	Copper 	There is not enough information	2
16	1	Who sells the cheapest noodles?	 Jolene 	 Fanella	There is not enough information	3	"Tommy has lost his backpack, he is standing in front of the posters facing them, which way does he need to go to find his backpack? "	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	The food festival is held	Yearly	Monthly 	There is not enough information	1
16	2	Who sells the cheapest noodles?	 Jolene 	 Fanella	There is not enough information	1	"Tommy has lost his backpack, he is standing in front of the posters facing them, which way does he need to go to find his backpack? "	Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	The food festival is held	Yearly	Monthly 	There is not enough information	1
16	3	Who sells the cheapest noodles?	 Jolene 	 Fanella	There is not enough information	3	"Tommy has lost his backpack, he is standing in front of the posters facing them, which way does he need to go to find his backpack? "	Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	The food festival is held	Yearly	Monthly 	There is not enough information	1
16	4	Who sells the cheapest noodles?	 Jolene 	 Fanella	There is not enough information	1	"Tommy has lost his backpack, he is standing in front of the posters facing them, which way does he need to go to find his backpack? "	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	The food festival is held	Yearly	Monthly 	There is not enough information	1
16	5	"Tommy has lost his backpack, he is standing in front of the posters facing them, which way does he need to go to find his backpack? "	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	Who sells the cheapest noodles?	 Jolene 	 Fanella	There is not enough information	3	The food festival is held	Yearly	Monthly 	There is not enough information	1
16	6	"Tommy has lost his backpack, he is standing in front of the posters facing them, which way does he need to go to find his backpack? "	Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	Who sells the cheapest noodles?	 Jolene 	 Fanella	There is not enough information	1	The food festival is held	Yearly	Monthly 	There is not enough information	1
16	7	"Tommy has lost his backpack, he is standing in front of the posters facing them, which way does he need to go to find his backpack? "	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	Who sells the cheapest noodles?	 Jolene 	 Fanella	There is not enough information	1	The food festival is held	Yearly	Monthly 	There is not enough information	1
16	8	"Tommy has lost his backpack, he is standing in front of the posters facing them, which way does he need to go to find his backpack? "	Left	Right	There is not enough information	2	Who sells the cheapest noodles?	 Jolene 	 Fanella	There is not enough information	3	The food festival is held	Yearly	Monthly 	There is not enough information	1
17	1	"Rockport's tourism board wants to advertise the local festivals in a county newspaper, which is the most popular festival in Rockport?"	The folk music festival 	 The sailing festival 	There is not enough information	3	All of the teams are competent and skilled but which team is most likely to win the race? 	The blue team	The green team	There is not enough information	3	Rockport has ___	Many events that take place throughout the year	One event that takes place throughout the year	There is not enough information	1
17	2	"Rockport's tourism board wants to advertise the local festivals in a county newspaper, which is the most popular festival in Rockport?"	The folk music festival 	 The sailing festival 	There is not enough information	1	All of the teams are competent and skilled but which team is most likely to win the race? 	The blue team	The green team	There is not enough information	1	Rockport has ___	Many events that take place throughout the year	One event that takes place throughout the year	There is not enough information	1
17	3	"Rockport's tourism board wants to advertise the local festivals in a county newspaper, which is the most popular festival in Rockport?"	The folk music festival 	 The sailing festival 	There is not enough information	3	All of the teams are competent and skilled but which team is most likely to win the race? 	The blue team	The green team	There is not enough information	1	Rockport has ___	Many events that take place throughout the year	One event that takes place throughout the year	There is not enough information	1
17	4	"Rockport's tourism board wants to advertise the local festivals in a county newspaper, which is the most popular festival in Rockport?"	The folk music festival 	 The sailing festival 	There is not enough information	1	All of the teams are competent and skilled but which team is most likely to win the race? 	The blue team	The green team	There is not enough information	3	Rockport has ___	Many events that take place throughout the year	One event that takes place throughout the year	There is not enough information	1
17	5	All of the teams are competent and skilled but which team is most likely to win the race? 	The blue team	The green team	There is not enough information	3	"Rockport's tourism board wants to advertise the local festivals in a county newspaper, which is the most popular festival in Rockport?"	The folk music festival 	 The sailing festival 	There is not enough information	3	Rockport has ___	Many events that take place throughout the year	One event that takes place throughout the year	There is not enough information	1
17	6	All of the teams are competent and skilled but which team is most likely to win the race? 	The blue team	The green team	There is not enough information	1	"Rockport's tourism board wants to advertise the local festivals in a county newspaper, which is the most popular festival in Rockport?"	The folk music festival 	 The sailing festival 	There is not enough information	1	Rockport has ___	Many events that take place throughout the year	One event that takes place throughout the year	There is not enough information	1
17	7	All of the teams are competent and skilled but which team is most likely to win the race? 	The blue team	The green team	There is not enough information	3	"Rockport's tourism board wants to advertise the local festivals in a county newspaper, which is the most popular festival in Rockport?"	The folk music festival 	 The sailing festival 	There is not enough information	1	Rockport has ___	Many events that take place throughout the year	One event that takes place throughout the year	There is not enough information	1
17	8	All of the teams are competent and skilled but which team is most likely to win the race? 	The blue team	The green team	There is not enough information	1	"Rockport's tourism board wants to advertise the local festivals in a county newspaper, which is the most popular festival in Rockport?"	The folk music festival 	 The sailing festival 	There is not enough information	3	Rockport has ___	Many events that take place throughout the year	One event that takes place throughout the year	There is not enough information	1
18	1	Which local company is likely to put the least amount of money toward tourism board’s Project?	Farmer Jack’s farm	 The bus company 	There is not enough information	3	A local archaeologist is has gone to the patch of grass that is the new potential dig site to investigate further but has forgotten his water bottle at the rest stop. Which way does he need to go to get his water?	Up the hill	Down the hill 	There is not enough information	3	The Kingsley Hills tourism board wants to build a 	Picknick area 	Museum 	There is not enough information	2
18	2	Which local company is likely to put the least amount of money toward tourism board’s Project?	Farmer Jack’s farm	 The bus company 	There is not enough information	1	A local archaeologist is has gone to the patch of grass that is the new potential dig site to investigate further but has forgotten his water bottle at the rest stop. Which way does he need to go to get his water?	Up the hill	Down the hill 	There is not enough information	2	The Kingsley Hills tourism board wants to build a 	Picknick area 	Museum 	There is not enough information	2
18	3	Which local company is likely to put the least amount of money toward tourism board’s Project?	Farmer Jack’s farm	 The bus company 	There is not enough information	3	A local archaeologist is has gone to the patch of grass that is the new potential dig site to investigate further but has forgotten his water bottle at the rest stop. Which way does he need to go to get his water?	Up the hill	Down the hill 	There is not enough information	2	The Kingsley Hills tourism board wants to build a 	Picknick area 	Museum 	There is not enough information	2
18	4	Which local company is likely to put the least amount of money toward tourism board’s Project?	Farmer Jack’s farm	 The bus company 	There is not enough information	1	A local archaeologist is has gone to the patch of grass that is the new potential dig site to investigate further but has forgotten his water bottle at the rest stop. Which way does he need to go to get his water?	Up the hill	Down the hill 	There is not enough information	3	The Kingsley Hills tourism board wants to build a 	Picknick area 	Museum 	There is not enough information	2
18	5	A local archaeologist is has gone to the patch of grass that is the new potential dig site to investigate further but has forgotten his water bottle at the rest stop. Which way does he need to go to get his water?	Up the hill	Down the hill 	There is not enough information	3	Which local company is likely to put the least amount of money toward tourism board’s Project?	Farmer Jack’s farm	 The bus company 	There is not enough information	3	The Kingsley Hills tourism board wants to build a 	Picknick area 	Museum 	There is not enough information	2
18	6	A local archaeologist is has gone to the patch of grass that is the new potential dig site to investigate further but has forgotten his water bottle at the rest stop. Which way does he need to go to get his water?	Up the hill	Down the hill 	There is not enough information	2	Which local company is likely to put the least amount of money toward tourism board’s Project?	Farmer Jack’s farm	 The bus company 	There is not enough information	1	The Kingsley Hills tourism board wants to build a 	Picknick area 	Museum 	There is not enough information	2
18	7	A local archaeologist is has gone to the patch of grass that is the new potential dig site to investigate further but has forgotten his water bottle at the rest stop. Which way does he need to go to get his water?	Up the hill	Down the hill 	There is not enough information	3	Which local company is likely to put the least amount of money toward tourism board’s Project?	Farmer Jack’s farm	 The bus company 	There is not enough information	1	The Kingsley Hills tourism board wants to build a 	Picknick area 	Museum 	There is not enough information	2
18	8	A local archaeologist is has gone to the patch of grass that is the new potential dig site to investigate further but has forgotten his water bottle at the rest stop. Which way does he need to go to get his water?	Up the hill	Down the hill 	There is not enough information	2	Which local company is likely to put the least amount of money toward tourism board’s Project?	Farmer Jack’s farm	 The bus company 	There is not enough information	3	The Kingsley Hills tourism board wants to build a 	Picknick area 	Museum 	There is not enough information	2
19	1	All of the McMurphy’s are liked by their patrons but who is the least popular? 	Frank	Susan	There is not enough information	3	"Susan has just put her favourite song on the jukebox, she now wants to have a beer. Which way does she need to go to reach the bar?"	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	The pub is called___	Frank's Pub	McMurphy's pub	There is not enough information	2
19	2	All of the McMurphy’s are liked by their patrons but who is the least popular? 	Frank	Susan	There is not enough information	1	"Susan has just put her favourite song on the jukebox, she now wants to have a beer. Which way does she need to go to reach the bar?"	Left	Right	There is not enough information	1	The pub is called___	Frank's Pub	McMurphy's pub	There is not enough information	2
19	3	All of the McMurphy’s are liked by their patrons but who is the least popular? 	Frank	Susan	There is not enough information	3	"Susan has just put her favourite song on the jukebox, she now wants to have a beer. Which way does she need to go to reach the bar?"	Left	Right	There is not enough information	1	The pub is called___	Frank's Pub	McMurphy's pub	There is not enough information	2
19	4	All of the McMurphy’s are liked by their patrons but who is the least popular? 	Frank	Susan	There is not enough information	1	"Susan has just put her favourite song on the jukebox, she now wants to have a beer. Which way does she need to go to reach the bar?"	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	The pub is called___	Frank's Pub	McMurphy's pub	There is not enough information	2
19	5	"Susan has just put her favourite song on the jukebox, she now wants to have a beer. Which way does she need to go to reach the bar?"	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	All of the McMurphy’s are liked by their patrons but who is the least popular? 	Frank	Susan	There is not enough information	3	The pub is called___	Frank's Pub	McMurphy's pub	There is not enough information	2
19	6	"Susan has just put her favourite song on the jukebox, she now wants to have a beer. Which way does she need to go to reach the bar?"	Left	Right	There is not enough information	1	All of the McMurphy’s are liked by their patrons but who is the least popular? 	Frank	Susan	There is not enough information	1	The pub is called___	Frank's Pub	McMurphy's pub	There is not enough information	2
19	7	"Susan has just put her favourite song on the jukebox, she now wants to have a beer. Which way does she need to go to reach the bar?"	Left	Right	There is not enough information	3	All of the McMurphy’s are liked by their patrons but who is the least popular? 	Frank	Susan	There is not enough information	1	The pub is called___	Frank's Pub	McMurphy's pub	There is not enough information	2
19	8	"Susan has just put her favourite song on the jukebox, she now wants to have a beer. Which way does she need to go to reach the bar?"	Left	Right	There is not enough information	1	All of the McMurphy’s are liked by their patrons but who is the least popular? 	Frank	Susan	There is not enough information	3	The pub is called___	Frank's Pub	McMurphy's pub	There is not enough information	2
20	1	"A new captain wants to hire a local fisherman who knows the waters, whom should he approach? "	Melvin	Herman	There is not enough information	3	Which sailing boat from Rockport is most likely to be the fastest? 	The King Charles	The Fast Kitten	There is not enough information	3	The fishermen of Rockport are not out at sea because____	There is a storm	The regatta is taking place	There is not enough information	2
20	2	"A new captain wants to hire a local fisherman who knows the waters, whom should he approach? "	Melvin	Herman	There is not enough information	2	Which sailing boat from Rockport is most likely to be the fastest? 	The King Charles	The Fast Kitten	There is not enough information	1	The fishermen of Rockport are not out at sea because____	There is a storm	The regatta is taking place	There is not enough information	2
20	3	"A new captain wants to hire a local fisherman who knows the waters, whom should he approach? "	Melvin	Herman	There is not enough information	3	Which sailing boat from Rockport is most likely to be the fastest? 	The King Charles	The Fast Kitten	There is not enough information	1	The fishermen of Rockport are not out at sea because____	There is a storm	The regatta is taking place	There is not enough information	2
20	4	"A new captain wants to hire a local fisherman who knows the waters, whom should he approach? "	Melvin	Herman	There is not enough information	2	Which sailing boat from Rockport is most likely to be the fastest? 	The King Charles	The Fast Kitten	There is not enough information	3	The fishermen of Rockport are not out at sea because____	There is a storm	The regatta is taking place	There is not enough information	2
20	5	Which sailing boat from Rockport is most likely to be the fastest? 	The King Charles	The Fast Kitten	There is not enough information	3	"A new captain wants to hire a local fisherman who knows the waters, whom should he approach? "	Melvin	Herman	There is not enough information	3	The fishermen of Rockport are not out at sea because____	There is a storm	The regatta is taking place	There is not enough information	2
20	6	Which sailing boat from Rockport is most likely to be the fastest? 	The King Charles	The Fast Kitten	There is not enough information	1	"A new captain wants to hire a local fisherman who knows the waters, whom should he approach? "	Melvin	Herman	There is not enough information	2	The fishermen of Rockport are not out at sea because____	There is a storm	The regatta is taking place	There is not enough information	2
20	7	Which sailing boat from Rockport is most likely to be the fastest? 	The King Charles	The Fast Kitten	There is not enough information	3	"A new captain wants to hire a local fisherman who knows the waters, whom should he approach? "	Melvin	Herman	There is not enough information	2	The fishermen of Rockport are not out at sea because____	There is a storm	The regatta is taking place	There is not enough information	2
20	8	Which sailing boat from Rockport is most likely to be the fastest? 	The King Charles	The Fast Kitten	There is not enough information	1	"A new captain wants to hire a local fisherman who knows the waters, whom should he approach? "	Melvin	Herman	There is not enough information	3	The fishermen of Rockport are not out at sea because____	There is a storm	The regatta is taking place	There is not enough information	2
21	1	Which Nation’s team is the least funded team exploring Dogger bank?	Great Britian’s	Demark’s	There is not enough information	3	"A diver that was having a few problems at the surface has now reached the remote control submarine. She wants to reach the other divers, does she need to go up or down?"	Up	Down	There is not enough information	3	Dogger bank is___	 An Island	 Under water	There is not enough information	2
21	2	Which Nation’s team is the least funded team exploring Dogger bank?	Great Britian’s	Demark’s	There is not enough information	1	"A diver that was having a few problems at the surface has now reached the remote control submarine. She wants to reach the other divers, does she need to go up or down?"	Up	Down	There is not enough information	2	Dogger bank is___	 An Island	 Under water	There is not enough information	2
21	3	Which Nation’s team is the least funded team exploring Dogger bank?	Great Britian’s	Demark’s	There is not enough information	3	"A diver that was having a few problems at the surface has now reached the remote control submarine. She wants to reach the other divers, does she need to go up or down?"	Up	Down	There is not enough information	2	Dogger bank is___	 An Island	 Under water	There is not enough information	2
21	4	Which Nation’s team is the least funded team exploring Dogger bank?	Great Britian’s	Demark’s	There is not enough information	1	"A diver that was having a few problems at the surface has now reached the remote control submarine. She wants to reach the other divers, does she need to go up or down?"	Up	Down	There is not enough information	3	Dogger bank is___	 An Island	 Under water	There is not enough information	2
21	5	"A diver that was having a few problems at the surface has now reached the remote control submarine. She wants to reach the other divers, does she need to go up or down?"	Up	Down	There is not enough information	3	Which Nation’s team is the least funded team exploring Dogger bank?	Great Britian’s	Demark’s	There is not enough information	3	Dogger bank is___	 An Island	 Under water	There is not enough information	2
21	6	"A diver that was having a few problems at the surface has now reached the remote control submarine. She wants to reach the other divers, does she need to go up or down?"	Up	Down	There is not enough information	2	Which Nation’s team is the least funded team exploring Dogger bank?	Great Britian’s	Demark’s	There is not enough information	1	Dogger bank is___	 An Island	 Under water	There is not enough information	2
21	7	"A diver that was having a few problems at the surface has now reached the remote control submarine. She wants to reach the other divers, does she need to go up or down?"	Up	Down	There is not enough information	3	Which Nation’s team is the least funded team exploring Dogger bank?	Great Britian’s	Demark’s	There is not enough information	1	Dogger bank is___	 An Island	 Under water	There is not enough information	2
21	8	"A diver that was having a few problems at the surface has now reached the remote control submarine. She wants to reach the other divers, does she need to go up or down?"	Up	Down	There is not enough information	2	Which Nation’s team is the least funded team exploring Dogger bank?	Great Britian’s	Demark’s	There is not enough information	3	Dogger bank is___	 An Island	 Under water	There is not enough information	2
22	1	Who is least likely to come in and help with the catering?	Amanda 	Jess	There is not enough information	3	The lifeguard wants to quickly check everything is up to scratch and is standing infront of the water filter facing the pool. In which direction does he need to look to find the loose paving slab? 	Left	Right 	There is not enough information	3	The pool has recently been refurbished before___	The start of summer	The start of winter	There is not enough information	1
22	2	Who is least likely to come in and help with the catering?	Amanda 	Jess	There is not enough information	1	The lifeguard wants to quickly check everything is up to scratch and is standing infront of the water filter facing the pool. In which direction does he need to look to find the loose paving slab? 	Left	Right 	There is not enough information	1	The pool has recently been refurbished before___	The start of summer	The start of winter	There is not enough information	1
22	3	Who is least likely to come in and help with the catering?	Amanda 	Jess	There is not enough information	3	The lifeguard wants to quickly check everything is up to scratch and is standing infront of the water filter facing the pool. In which direction does he need to look to find the loose paving slab? 	Left	Right 	There is not enough information	1	The pool has recently been refurbished before___	The start of summer	The start of winter	There is not enough information	1
22	4	Who is least likely to come in and help with the catering?	Amanda 	Jess	There is not enough information	1	The lifeguard wants to quickly check everything is up to scratch and is standing infront of the water filter facing the pool. In which direction does he need to look to find the loose paving slab? 	Left	Right 	There is not enough information	3	The pool has recently been refurbished before___	The start of summer	The start of winter	There is not enough information	1
22	5	The lifeguard wants to quickly check everything is up to scratch and is standing infront of the water filter facing the pool. In which direction does he need to look to find the loose paving slab? 	Left	Right 	There is not enough information	3	Who is least likely to come in and help with the catering?	Amanda 	Jess	There is not enough information	3	The pool has recently been refurbished before___	The start of summer	The start of winter	There is not enough information	1
22	6	The lifeguard wants to quickly check everything is up to scratch and is standing infront of the water filter facing the pool. In which direction does he need to look to find the loose paving slab? 	Left	Right 	There is not enough information	1	Who is least likely to come in and help with the catering?	Amanda 	Jess	There is not enough information	1	The pool has recently been refurbished before___	The start of summer	The start of winter	There is not enough information	1
22	7	The lifeguard wants to quickly check everything is up to scratch and is standing infront of the water filter facing the pool. In which direction does he need to look to find the loose paving slab? 	Left	Right 	There is not enough information	3	Who is least likely to come in and help with the catering?	Amanda 	Jess	There is not enough information	1	The pool has recently been refurbished before___	The start of summer	The start of winter	There is not enough information	1
22	8	The lifeguard wants to quickly check everything is up to scratch and is standing infront of the water filter facing the pool. In which direction does he need to look to find the loose paving slab? 	Left	Right 	There is not enough information	1	Who is least likely to come in and help with the catering?	Amanda 	Jess	There is not enough information	3	The pool has recently been refurbished before___	The start of summer	The start of winter	There is not enough information	1
23	1	Who is likely to pledge the least in support of the Gallery?	Fred	Simon 	There is not enough information	3	Fred is standing by the Sculpture made of drifwood which way does he need to go to get to the sculpture made of plastic bottles?	Towards the sculpture of the whale 	Away from the sculpture of the whale 	There is not enough information	3	The Gallery of Innsmouth is hosting famous artists from____	Overseas	The local area	There is not enough information	2
23	2	Who is likely to pledge the least in support of the Gallery?	Fred	Simon 	There is not enough information	1	Fred is standing by the Sculpture made of drifwood which way does he need to go to get to the sculpture made of plastic bottles?	Towards the sculpture of the whale 	Away from the sculpture of the whale 	There is not enough information	1	The Gallery of Innsmouth is hosting famous artists from____	Overseas	The local area	There is not enough information	2
23	3	Who is likely to pledge the least in support of the Gallery?	Fred	Simon 	There is not enough information	3	Fred is standing by the Sculpture made of drifwood which way does he need to go to get to the sculpture made of plastic bottles?	Towards the sculpture of the whale 	Away from the sculpture of the whale 	There is not enough information	1	The Gallery of Innsmouth is hosting famous artists from____	Overseas	The local area	There is not enough information	2
23	4	Who is likely to pledge the least in support of the Gallery?	Fred	Simon 	There is not enough information	1	Fred is standing by the Sculpture made of drifwood which way does he need to go to get to the sculpture made of plastic bottles?	Towards the sculpture of the whale 	Away from the sculpture of the whale 	There is not enough information	3	The Gallery of Innsmouth is hosting famous artists from____	Overseas	The local area	There is not enough information	2
23	5	Fred is standing by the Sculpture made of drifwood which way does he need to go to get to the sculpture made of plastic bottles?	Towards the sculpture of the whale 	Away from the sculpture of the whale 	There is not enough information	3	Who is likely to pledge the least in support of the Gallery?	Fred	Simon 	There is not enough information	3	The Gallery of Innsmouth is hosting famous artists from____	Overseas	The local area	There is not enough information	2
23	6	Fred is standing by the Sculpture made of drifwood which way does he need to go to get to the sculpture made of plastic bottles?	Towards the sculpture of the whale 	Away from the sculpture of the whale 	There is not enough information	1	Who is likely to pledge the least in support of the Gallery?	Fred	Simon 	There is not enough information	1	The Gallery of Innsmouth is hosting famous artists from____	Overseas	The local area	There is not enough information	2
23	7	Fred is standing by the Sculpture made of drifwood which way does he need to go to get to the sculpture made of plastic bottles?	Towards the sculpture of the whale 	Away from the sculpture of the whale 	There is not enough information	3	Who is likely to pledge the least in support of the Gallery?	Fred	Simon 	There is not enough information	1	The Gallery of Innsmouth is hosting famous artists from____	Overseas	The local area	There is not enough information	2
23	8	Fred is standing by the Sculpture made of drifwood which way does he need to go to get to the sculpture made of plastic bottles?	Towards the sculpture of the whale 	Away from the sculpture of the whale 	There is not enough information	1	Who is likely to pledge the least in support of the Gallery?	Fred	Simon 	There is not enough information	3	The Gallery of Innsmouth is hosting famous artists from____	Overseas	The local area	There is not enough information	2
24	1	The wedding will have many speeches but who is likely to tell the best story? 	Aaron	Josephine	There is not enough information	3	Which type of tree in the cemetery is the tallest?	Oak	Birch	There is not enough information	3	The cemetery is a popular spot for___	Weddings	 Youths to go drinking	There is not enough information	1
24	2	The wedding will have many speeches but who is likely to tell the best story? 	Aaron	Josephine	There is not enough information	2	Which type of tree in the cemetery is the tallest?	Oak	Birch	There is not enough information	1	The cemetery is a popular spot for___	Weddings	 Youths to go drinking	There is not enough information	1
24	3	The wedding will have many speeches but who is likely to tell the best story? 	Aaron	Josephine	There is not enough information	3	Which type of tree in the cemetery is the tallest?	Oak	Birch	There is not enough information	1	The cemetery is a popular spot for___	Weddings	 Youths to go drinking	There is not enough information	1
24	4	The wedding will have many speeches but who is likely to tell the best story? 	Aaron	Josephine	There is not enough information	2	Which type of tree in the cemetery is the tallest?	Oak	Birch	There is not enough information	3	The cemetery is a popular spot for___	Weddings	 Youths to go drinking	There is not enough information	1
24	5	Which type of tree in the cemetery is the tallest?	Oak	Birch	There is not enough information	3	The wedding will have many speeches but who is likely to tell the best story? 	Aaron	Josephine	There is not enough information	3	The cemetery is a popular spot for___	Weddings	 Youths to go drinking	There is not enough information	1
24	6	Which type of tree in the cemetery is the tallest?	Oak	Birch	There is not enough information	1	The wedding will have many speeches but who is likely to tell the best story? 	Aaron	Josephine	There is not enough information	2	The cemetery is a popular spot for___	Weddings	 Youths to go drinking	There is not enough information	1
24	7	Which type of tree in the cemetery is the tallest?	Oak	Birch	There is not enough information	3	The wedding will have many speeches but who is likely to tell the best story? 	Aaron	Josephine	There is not enough information	2	The cemetery is a popular spot for___	Weddings	 Youths to go drinking	There is not enough information	1
24	8	Which type of tree in the cemetery is the tallest?	Oak	Birch	There is not enough information	1	The wedding will have many speeches but who is likely to tell the best story? 	Aaron	Josephine	There is not enough information	3	The cemetery is a popular spot for___	Weddings	 Youths to go drinking	There is not enough information	1
